(Bernadette:)Get that guy! Get that guy!
Pew, pew, pew!
Uh, Dr. Rostenkowski,
it may interest you to know...
...that saying, "Pew, pew, pew," isn't
as effective as pressing your blaster key.
ln the same way that saying, "Whee,"
doesn't make the landspeeder go.
(Bernadette:)Pew!
- Raj, lmperial Troopers on your tail.
Unh. Got him.
(Raj:)When Gandhi advocated
his philosophy of nonviolence...
...l bet he didn't know how much fun
it was killing stuff.
(Leonard:)All right, I think we got them all.
Let's divide up the loot.
(Bernadette:)Ooh, look at
this pretty purple robe I just got.
(Bernadette:)You should put on yours
and then we'll match.
But I worked hard to get this armor, heh.
(Bernadette:)Sorry, I just thought it'd be nice
if people knew we were a couple.
(Howard:)Fine, I'll change.